

- □ rakib063049@gmail.com
- bd.linkedin.com/in/rokibulhassan
- ngithub.com/rokibulhassan
- http://goo.gl/aZcsQM
- □ +8801532063049

Summary

I am Self-motivated Full stack Ruby on Rails developer with back-end, front-end and server management skills.

Skilled Ruby on Rails developer with over Five years experience in dynamic web applications development. Worked well on projects with team as well as self built projects from scratch to the production stage with full efficiency of TDD & BDD.

Work History

Cefalo

Software Engineer

August 2015 - Present

Currently I am looking after jobb.tu.no an popular jobs portal in Norway. My responsibilities are attend scrum, meet feature request, take care of existing bug, ensure regular performance enhancement through refactoring, upgrading technologies, writing test codes etc., deployment,

Tasawr Interactive

Software Engineer

December 2012 - August 2015

I was an important team player, attend scrum, learn new technology, System design and development, add new features, bug fixing, write automated test.

Nascenia IT

Software Engineer

February 2012 - December 2012

In Nascenia as a team player I did following activities attend scrum, learn new technology, manage projects, debugging, bug fixing, write automated test.

iBridge BD Technology

Jr. Software Engineer

July 2011 - January 2012

Technical Skills

Ruby jQuery C/C++ Ajax

C# Twitter Bootstrap

Ruby on RailsCSSMySqlHamlMongoDBSlimElasticsearchgit

Stripe

Education

Rajshahi University of Engineering & Technology (RUET)

M.Sc. in CSE

I am attending my master programm for session 2014-2016

Rajshahi University of Engineering & Technology (RUET)

B.Sc. in CSE

I have completed my graduate in 2011

Projects

TU Jobs

[Ruby on Rails, Mysql, MongoDB, HTML, Ajax, JQuery, JavaScript] http://jobb.tu.no
Teknisk Ukehlad Media As (www.tu.no) is the publish

Teknisk Ukeblad Media As (www.tu.no) is the publisher of TUJOBS.com and Teknisk Ukeblad, Norway's leading technology and business magazine.

Moteel

[Ruby on Rails, Mysql, MongoDB, HTML, Ajax, JQuery, JavaScript] http://moteel.com

Moteel makes hotel revenue generation easy by offering hoteliers Hotel Management, Booking Engine, Website, Channel Integration, and more.

SnapKnot

[Ruby on Rails 1.8.7, Mysql, HTML, Haml, Ajax, JQuery, JavaScript] http://snapknot.com

Find the best local wedding photographers. Get prices and see sample wedding photography portfolios in our directory.

${\tt Simple Sign Up}$

[Ruby on Rails 1.8.7, Mysql, HTML, Ajax, JQuery, JavaScript] http://simplesignup.se

Simple Signup helps you with bookings and payments fast

and easy. Create event and invite people; Participants sign up and pay online.

TipHive

[Ruby on Rails, Mysql, MongoDB, HTML, Ajax, JQuery, JavaScript] https://tiphive.com
TipHive is a friend-powered community for finding the best tips. Top 10 logo university. At School · At Work. Home bird.

That Way Hat

[Ruby on Rails, Mysql, MongoDB, HTML, Ajax, JQuery, JavaScript] https://thatwayhat.com
That Way Hat's free account let's you display your hats on your own store page.

Reference

Prasenjit Kumar Nag

Ruby Developer Trike Apps joycse06@gmail.com

Declaration

I hereby declare that the above written particulars are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Rokibul Hasan February 2017

Tags: RubyMine, Caching, Rspec, cumcumber, database design, deployment, capistrano, Paypal, jQuery, Ajax, html, haml, MVC, XML, JSON, Agile, XP, TDD, BDD, Refactoring, git, PivotalTracker, Trelo, Asana, Redis.